Finding Aid for the C. Franklyn Zeek Collection
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
C. Franklyn Zeek Collection
1942-1951
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0540
.05 linear feet
Scope and Contents
This collection contains six journal articles written by C. Franklyn Zeek. They are arranged in alphabetical order, by title.
- Journal Articles
  - Balzac as a Business Man
    - reprinted from The French Review, December, 1951
  - Democracy and Religion
    - reprinted from The French Review, February, 1944
  - The Great Writers of the “Siecle De Louis XIV” How Much Did They Owe To Their King?
    - reprinted from The French Review, March, 1942
  - Is French Literature Passee?
    - reprinted from Peabody Journal of Education, January, 1942
  - Palissot and Voltaire
    - reprinted from Modern Language Quarterly, December, 1949
  - What of Foreign Languages Now?
    - reprinted from The Tennessee Teacher, April, 1943